{
  "Simple": {
    "Numeric": [
      {
        "Question": "How many cards are in a deck",
        "Answer": 78
      },
      {
        "Question": "How many court cards are in a deck",
        "Answer": 16
      },
      {
        "Question": "How many major arcana cards are in a deck",
        "Answer": 22
      },
      {
        "Question": "How many minor arcana cards are in a deck",
        "Answer": 56
      },
      {
        "Question": "How many pips are in a deck",
        "Answer": 40
      }
    ],
    "MultipleChoice": [
      {
        "Question": "What is the name of the collection of cards named page, knight, queen, and king, present in each of the 4 suits",
        "Answer": "Court",
        "IncorrectChoices": [
          "House",
          "Castle",
          "Congress",
          "High"
        ]
      },
      {
        "Question": "What is the name of the collection of cards numbered ace through ten, present in each of the 4 suits",
        "Answer": "Pips",
        "IncorrectChoices": [
          "Pops",
          "Parts",
          "Lesser",
          "Low"
        ]
      },
      {
        "Question": "What is the closest meaning of Arcana",
        "Answer": "Secrets",
        "IncorrectChoices": [
          "Mysteries",
          "Illusions",
          "Distractions",
          "Magic"
        ]
      },
      {
        "Question": "What is the closest meaning of Arcana",
        "Answer": "Secret",
        "IncorrectChoices": [
          "Mystery",
          "Illusion",
          "Distraction",
          "Magic"
        ]
      },
      {
        "Question": "What is the name of the person asking the question",
        "Answer": "Querent",
        "IncorrectChoices": [
          "Quarrant",
          "Questioner",
          "Interrogator",
          "Querier"
        ]
      },
      {
        "Question": "What is the name of the person performing the reading",
        "Answer": "Reader",
        "IncorrectChoices": [
          "Teller",
          "Witch",
          "Seer",
          "Warlock"
        ]
      },
      {
        "Question": "What is the name of a card that appears upside down to the person performing the reading",
        "Answer": "Reversal or reversed",
        "IncorrectChoices": [
          "Inversal or inverse",
          "Flipped or upside-down",
          "Wrong or upsetting",
          "Cursed or damned"
        ]
      },
      {
        "Question": "What is the name of a diagram of card layout and description of position significance and purpose",
        "Answer": "Spread",
        "IncorrectChoices": [
          "Chart",
          "See",
          "Alignment",
          "Call"
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  "CardSpecific": {
    "Major": [
      {
        "Number": 0,
        "Name": "The Fool",
        "Keywords": [
          "Beginnings",
          "Innocence",
          "Freedom",
          "Spontaneity",
          "Adventure",
          "Youth",
          "Idealism",
          "Faith",
          "Purity",
          "Fearlessness",
          "Carelessness",
          "Eccentricity",
          "Apparent foolishness"
        ],
        "Reversed": [
          "Folly",
          "Foolishness",
          "Carelessness",
          "Stupidity",
          "Negligence",
          "Distraction",
          "Naivety",
          "Recklessness",
          "Risk-taking"
        ],
        "Astrological": "Uranus",
        "Element": "Air",
        "RiderWaiteSmithSymbolism": [
          {
            "Component": "White dog",
            "Associations": [
              "Inner voice",
              "Distractions"
            ]
          },
          {
            "Component": "Sun",
            "Associations": [
              "Joy",
              "Optimism"
            ]
          },
          {
            "Component": "Stick with bag",
            "Associations": [
              "Lessons from previous lives",
              "Innate abilities"
            ]
          },
          {
            "Component": "Red feather in cap",
            "Associations": [
              "Passion",
              "Heart"
            ]
          },
          {
            "Component": "White rose",
            "Associations": [
              "Purity"
            ]
          },
          {
            "Component": "Cliff",
            "Associations": [
              "Leap of faith"
            ]
          },
          {
            "Component": "Brightly colored clothing",
            "Associations": [
              "Unique",
              "Careless",
              "Eccentric nature"
            ]
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "Number": 0,
        "Name": "The Magician",
        "Keywords": [
          "Will",
          "Talent",
          "Skill",
          "Creativity",
          "Manifestation",
          "Communication",
          "Magic",
          "Action",
          "Awareness",
          "Power",
          "Resourcefulness",
          "Concentration",
          "Eloquence"
        ],
        "Reversed": [
          "Trickery",
          "Manipulation",
          "Deceit",
          "Con",
          "Liar",
          "Misuse of gifts"
        ],
        "Astrological": "Mercury",
        "Element": "Air",
        "RiderWaiteSmithSymbolism": [
          {
            "Component": "Red roses",
            "Associations": [
              "Passion"
            ]
          },
          {
            "Component": "White lilies",
            "Associations": [
              "Purity"
            ]
          },
          {
            "Component": "Lemniscate",
            "Associations": [
              "Infinite flow of energy"
            ]
          },
          {
            "Component": "Ouroboros",
            "Associations": [
              "Eternity",
              "Transformation"
            ]
          },
          {
            "Component": "Red and white clothing",
            "Associations": [
              "Passion",
              "Purity"
            ]
          },
          {
            "Component": "Wand in right hand",
            "Associations": [
              "Will"
            ]
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
}
